(water splashing)
(birds calling)
(steam horn blaring)
(drum sticks clacking)
(powerful rock music)
(upbeat powerful rock music)
♪ One man come in the name of love ♪
♪ One man come and go ♪
♪ One man come, he to justify ♪
♪ One man to overthrow ♪
♪ In the name of love ♪
♪ What more in the name of love ♪
♪ One man caught on a barbed wire fence ♪
♪ One man, he resist ♪
♪ One man washed on an empty beach ♪
♪ One man betrayed with a kiss ♪
♪ In the name of love ♪
♪ What more in the name of love ♪
♪ Nobody like you ♪
♪ There's no body like you ♪
(powerful upbeat rock music)
♪ Mm-mm-mm-mm, mm-mm-mm-mm ♪
♪ Mm-mm-mm-mm-mm ♪
♪ Early morning, April four ♪
♪ Shot rings out in the Memphis sky ♪
♪ Free at last, they took your life ♪
♪ They could not take your pride ♪
♪ In the name of love ♪
♪ What more in the name of love ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Mm-mm-mm-mm ♪
♪ Mm-mm ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Mm-mm-mm-mm ♪
♪ Mm-mm ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Mm-mm-mm-mm ♪